Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2017 RL.00924
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2011; 2399 Volumes
  - Top Secret/S.I., 140
    - Agent 13: Sourcebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 431)
    - Commando (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 428)
    - Commando: Brushfire Wars (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 433)
    - Covert Operations: Source Book (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 430)
    - Covert Operations: Source Book, Volume 2 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 427)
    - F.R.E.E. America (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 426)
    - Free Lancers (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 429)
    - G4 File: Guns, Gadgets, and Getaway Gear (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 432)
    - Operation: Starfire (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 436)
    - Orion Rising (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 434)
    - The Doomsday Drop (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 435)
    - The Final Weapon (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 440)
    - The Sting of the Spider (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 438)
    - The Web (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 458)
    - Web of Deceit (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 439)
    - Web Wars (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 437)
  - Traveller, 141
    - Adventure Class Ships Vol. 1 (FASA), undated (Box BG82)
    - Amycus Probe (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1479)
    - Aurore Sourcebook (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1987 (Volume 1522)
    - Beanstalk (Northfield, MN: Atlas Games), 1987 (Volume 1533)
    - Colonial Atlas (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1987 (Volume 1521)
    - Corsairs of the Turku Waste (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1467)
    - Crucis Margin (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1475)
    - Darkling Ship (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1477)
    - Darthanon Queen (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1469)
    - Doom of the Singing Star (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1482)
    - Drakne Station (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1468)
    - Encounters in the Corelian Quadrant (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1980 (Volume 1559)
    - Encounters in the Phoenix Quadrant (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1980 (Volume 1661)
    - Encounters in the Ventura Quadrant (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1980 (Volume 1560)
    - Energy Curve (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1987 (Volume 1523)
    - Fifty Starbases (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1470)
    - Geptorem (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1981 (Volume 1563)
    - Glimmerdrift Reaches (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1476)
    - Hydronaut (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), undated (Volume 1660)
    - Kafer Dawn (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1987 (Volume 1524)
    - Ley Sector (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1472)
    - Lomodo Four A (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1981 (Volume 1664)
    - Maranantha-Alkahest Sector (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1474)
    - Marooned on Ghostring (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1480)
    - Mission to Zephor (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1980 (Volume 1663)
    - Nithus (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1981 (Volume 1665)
    - Nystalux (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1981 (Volume 1668)
    - Pen-Latol's World: Adventure on an Alien Planet (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1980 (Volume 1662)
    - Port Xanatath (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1980 (Volume 1666)
    - Rogue Moon of Spinstorme (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1478)
    - Sapies (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1981 (Volume 1561)
    - Simba Safari (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1473)
    - Star Port Module Number One Hotel Complex (FASA), undated (Box BG82)
    - Tancred (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1466)
    - The Traveller Logbook (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1471)
    - Theta Borealis Sector (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1981 (Volume 1667)
    - Wabor Parn (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1981 (Volume 1562)
    - Waspwinter (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1481)
  - Tunnels and Trolls, 142
    - !Weirdworld! (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1717)
    - A Computer Generated Dungeon (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1709)
      2 versions
    - Arena of Khazan (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1710)
    - Beyond the Silvered Pane (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1716)
    - Beyond the Wall of Tears (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1984 (Volume 1166)
    - Blue Frog Tavern (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1701)
    - Buffalo Castle (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1721)
    - Catacombs of the Bear Cult: Level 1 (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1695)
    - Dargon's Dungeon (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1718)
    - Deathtrap Equalizer Dungeon, 1st ed. (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1712)
    - Gamesmen of Kasar (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1688)
    - Labyrinth (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1720)
    - Misty Wood (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1700)
    - Naked Doom (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1719)
    - Overkill (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1714)
    - Overkill: A Solitaire Adventure (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1715)
    - Rat on a Stick (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1496)
    - Sea of Mystery (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1702)
    - Sewers of Oblivion (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1703)
    - Sorcer Solitaire (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1713)
    - Sword for Hire (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1711)
    - The Dungeon of the Bear (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1746)
      loose paper
    - The Dungeon of the Bear Level 2 (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1747)
    - The Dungeon of the Bear Level 3 (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1748)
    - The Toughest Dungeon in the World (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1558)
    - Tunnels and Trolls / Goblin Lake (Solitaire Adventure) (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 2007 (Volume 1778)
      Free RPG Day
    - Tunnels and Trolls, 4th ed. (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1708)
    - Tunnels and Trolls, 5th edition (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1073)
    - Underground Doom (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1749)
  - Universe, 143
    - Adventure Guide (New York, NY: Simulations Publications, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1677)
    - Gamemasters' Guide (New York, NY: Simulations Publications, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1676)
  - Uttgart, 144
    - The Mountains of Ikurna (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), 1982 (Volume 1733)
    - The Ring of Gilrod (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), 1981 (Volume 1734)
  - Villains and Vigilantes, 145
    - Break in at Three Kilometer Island (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1498)
    - From the Deeps of Space (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1984 (Volume 1174)
    - Most Wanted, Vol. 1 (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1983 (Volume 1176)
    - The Dawn of DNA (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1984 (Volume 1175)
    - Villains and Vigilantes (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1979 (Volume 1679)
  - Vor the Maelstrom, 146
    - Growlers (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1999 (Volume 1287)
    - Neo-Soviet: Forcebook (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 2000 (Volume 1312)
    - Pharon: Forcebook (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 2000 (Volume 1314)
    - Razorfang's Exodus: Conflict Book (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 2000 (Volume 1310)
    - Shard: Forcebook (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 2000 (Volume 1306)
    - Union: Forcebook (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1999 (Volume 1313)
    - Vor The Maelstrom: Rulebook (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 2000 (Volume 1305)
    - Zykhee: Forcebook (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 2000 (Volume 1311)
  - Votoms, 147
    - Armored Trooper (no city: ANimechaniX), 1997 (Volume 723)
  - Wheel of Time, 148
    - Prophecies of the Dragon (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 110)
    - The Wheel of Time Roleplaying Game (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 109)
  - Worlds of the Eternal Champion, 149
    - Dragon Lords of Melnibone: Adventuring in a Dark World of Law and Chaos (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 2001 (Volume 111)
  - WyrdWorld, 150
    - Demon's Pawn (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), 1980 (Volume 1704)
    - Double-Doom (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), 1981 (Volume 1727)
    - Kahldath: The Messiah (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), undated (Volume 1706)
    - Ravenscate (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), undated (Volume 1728)
    - The Corsairs of Cythera (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), undated (Volume 1730)
    - The Maghrib (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), 1982 (Volume 1705)
  - Ysgarth, 151
    - Blood Tribute (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), 1981 (Volume 1732)
    - Ynisare (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), 1981 (Volume 1731)
  - Zulu, 152
    - Isandhlwana (Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications), 1979 (Volume M5)
    - Naka (Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications), 1979 (Volume M5)
    - Rorke's Drift (Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications), 1973 (Volume M5)
  - General Games, 62
    - 100 Bushels of Rye (Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications), 1988 (Volume 1179)
    - 3G3: Guns! Guns! Guns! (Richmond, VA: Blacksburg Tactical Research Center), 1991 (Volume 1352)
    - A Fistful of Turkeys (Cedar Park, TX: Some Turkey Games), 1981 (Volume 672)
    - A Game of Thrones: d20-based Open Gaming RPG (no place: White Wolf Publishing), 2005 (Volume 112)
    - A Modeler's Guide to Ancient and Medieval Ships to 1650 (Dana Point, CA: Moonraker Publications), 1981 (Volume 1580)
    - Abyss (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 677)
    - Aliens: Adventure Game (Pasadena, CA: Leading Edge Games), 1991 (Volume 1347)
    - All the Worlds' Monsters (Albany, CA: The Chaosium), 1977 (Volume M3)
    - All the Worlds' Monsters, 2nd ed. (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1620)
    - All the Worlds' Monsters, Vol. II (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1977 (Volume 1619)
    - All the Worlds' Monsters, Vol. III (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1980 (Volume 1618)
    - Amazon Mutual Wants You!, Vol. I (Abilene, TX: Dragon Tree Press), 1982 (Volume 1628)
    - Amber (Detroit, MI: Phage Press), 1991 (Volume 1369)
    - Annihilator and One World (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1979 (Volume 684)
    - Arden: A Complete Kingdom (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1979 (Volume 1349)
    - At Rapier's Point (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1993 (Volume 1445)
    - Authentic Thaumaturgy (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1722)
    - Barsoomian Battle Manual (Dallas, TX: Heritage Models, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1680)
    - Basic Role-Playing (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1080)
    - Battle for Basra (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1991 (Volume 1795)
    - Black Hole (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1978 (Volume 679)
    - Book of Fantasy Miniatures (Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games), 1978 (Volume 1764)
    - Book of Plots, Vol. I: Tavern Tales (Abilene, TX: Dragon Tree Press), 1983 (Volume 1585)
    - Building Complex Series 1: Corporation Building (no city: Seeker Gaming Systems), 1991 (Volume 1954)
    - Building Complex Series 2: Research Facility (no city: Seeker Gaming Systems), 1992 (Volume 1955)
    - Bunnies and Burrows: The Fantasy World of Intelligent Rabbits (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1976 (Volume 1674)
    - Campaign Law: Guidelines for Gamemasters (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1982 (Volume 1086)
    - Carse: Urban Aid for Fantasy Roleplaying (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1986 (Volume 1744)
    - Castle Arcania (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume M2)
    - Castle Book II (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1555)
    - Circle of Ice (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 678)
    - Cities, 2nd ed. (San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press), 1981 (Volume 1613)
    - Cities: A Gamemaster's Guide (San Diego, CA: Stephen Abrams), 1979 (Volume 1587)
    - Cities: Create and Explore your own Fantasy Communities (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1986 (Volume 1745)
    - City of Terrors (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1699)
    - City State of the World Emperor (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1692)
    - CityBook I: Butcher, Baker, Candlestick Maker (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1646)
    - CityBook II: Port o' Call (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1984 (Volume 1643)
    - CityBook III: Deadly Nightside (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1987 (Volume 1645)
    - Cloudland (Grenadier Models, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1139)
    - Corsair! A Game of Piracy and Plunder (unknown), 1977 (Volume M4)
    - Corsairs of Tallibar (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1505)
    - Dimensions and Doors (Peterborough, NH: Rider Fantasy Creations), 1979 (Volume 1689)
    - Dream Park (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1992 (Volume 1415)
    - Druids of Doom (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1500)
    - Duel Arcane (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords Ltd.), 1980 (Volume M2)
    - Dungeon Décor: Scenery for Role-playing Games and Dioramas (Agawam, MA: Falchion Products), 1978 (Volume M5)
    - F'deckFo's Tomb (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1492)
    - Fantastic Personalities (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1546)
    - Faster than Light (Madison Hts, Michigan: Tri Tac Inc.), 1982 (Volume M3)
    - Field Guide to Ecounters vol 2 (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1751)
      one color copy one black and white
    - Fire, Hack and Run: Universal Skirmish Rules (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1979 (Volume 1636)
    - Fringeworthy (Madison Hts, MI: Tri Tac, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1659)
    - Game Design, Vol. I: Theory and Practice (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1981 (Volume 1603)
    - Gear Krieg: Two-Fisted Pulp Superscience in a World At War! (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2000 (Volume 2205)
    - Gladiators (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1975 (Volume 1696)
    - Glory Hole Dwarven Mine (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1548)
    - Goblin Lake (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 681)
    - Grimtooth's Traps Too: A Game-Master's Aid (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1067)
    - Grimtooth's Traps: A Game-Master's Aid (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1066)
    - Guide to the City State (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1976 (Volume M4)
    - Gunfights in the Spirit of the Old West (Raleigh, NC: Argon Games), 1980 (Volume M2)
    - Gunslinger (Sarasota, FL: R. Sartore and Associates), 1978 (Volume M4)
    - Heart of the Sunken Lands (San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press), 1983 (Volume 1590)
    - Heroes: Unlimited (Detroit, MI: Palladium Books), 1984 (Volume 1085)
    - Heroic Expeditions (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1752)
    - High Colonies (Vancouver, BC: Waterford Publishing House, Ltd. ), 1988 (Volume 1350)
    - High Ranger Guard (Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1631)
    - Holy War (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1979 (Volume 680)
    - Hong Kong Action Theatre! (Lawrence, KS: Event Horizons Productions), 1996 (Volume 1444)
    - Ice War (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1978 (Volume 685)
    - In Search of Kelandor's Gold (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1465)
    - Invasion of the Air-Eaters (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1979 (Volume 687)
    - Ironhoof Highlands (Decatur, IL: Group One Games), 1981 (Volume 1573)
    - Jonril: Gateway to the Sunken Lands (San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press), 1982 (Volume 1588)
    - Junta: The Game of Power, Intrigue, Money and Revolution (New York, NY: Creative Wargames Workshop Inc.), 1979 (Volume M4)
    - Killer: The Game of Assassination (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1981 (Volume 1072)
    - Kung Fu 2100 (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1980 (Volume 674)
    - Lionheart: Living in History: England 1190 AD (Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications), 1987 (Volume 962)
    - Lords of the Middle Sea (Albany, CA: The Chaosium), 1978 (Volume M4)
    - Lythia (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1985 (Volume 1197)
    - Master Book Companion (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), undated (Volume 230)
    - Master Book: With the Worlds of Indiana Jones and Bloodshadows (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 595)
    - Masters of Mind (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1495)
    - Metamorphosis Alpha (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1976 (Volume 1675)
    - Mini-System 2: Character Role Playing (Washington, D.C.: Ragnarok Enterprises), 1981 (Volume 1729)
    - Miniature Rules (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 523)
    - Monday Morning Manager (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords Ltd.), 1980 (Volume M2)
    - Monsters! Monsters! (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1074)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 818)
    - Mountain of Mystery (Englewood, CO: Dimension Six, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1686)
    - Mug Book: The Game of Street Crimes (Denver, CO: Power Play Games), 1984 (Volume 1694)
    - Murder in Irliss (Reston, VA: Reston Publishing Company, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 1793)
    - Noir (no city: Archon Gaming, Inc. ), 1996 (Volume 1357)
    - Nomad Gods (Albany, CA: The Chaosium), 1977 (Volume M4)
    - Odysseus: Legendry and Mythology (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1980 (Volume 1065)
    - Ogre (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1977 (Volume 689)
    - One-Page Bulge (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1980 (Volume 673)
    - Overland Ecounters: Fifth through the Eighth Levels (Oakland, CA: The Fantasy Factory), 1979 (Volume M4)
    - Overland Ecounters: First through the Forth Levels (Oakland, CA: The Fantasy Factory), 1979 (Volume M4)
    - Palladium RPG Book III: Adventures on the High Seas (Detroit, MI: Palladium Books), 1987 (Volume 1351)
    - Pirates of Hagrost (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1557)
    - Places of Mystery II: Alluring Alcoves (Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1579)
    - Places of Mystery III: Sylvan Settings (Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1598)
    - Prey of Darkness (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1564)
    - Race to High Adventure Through Icy Arctic Seas: Icebergs Minigame (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1982 (Volume M2)
    - Raid on Iran (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1980 (Volume 671)
    - Raiders and Traders: the Heroic Age of Greece (Albany, CA: The Chaosium), 1979 (Volume M4)
    - Rapier and Dagger (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1978 (Volume 1691)
    - Ravenlon: Danger in the Dark Forest (Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1635)
    - Ravenscrag (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1503)
    - Recon (Lincoln, AR: RPG, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1077)
    - Reich Star (Charlotte, NC: Creative Encounters), 1990 (Volume 1348)
    - Reich: The Iron Dream of German Unification (Albany, CA: The Chaosium), 1979 (Volume M4)
    - Relive the Battle at the Alamo with Famous Frontier Heroes: Remember the Alamo Minigame (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1982 (Volume M2)
    - Restormel (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1538)
      small slip of paper with description of the map
    - Revolt on Antares: Science Fiction Minigame (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1981 (Volume M2)
    - Rivets (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1977 (Volume 686)
    - Sage: Age of Heroes Minigame (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1981 (Volume M2)
    - Search for the Crystal Sword (Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1632)
    - Search for the Lost City: A Jungle Adventure (Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1634)
    - Shield Maidens of Sea Rule (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1556)
    - Society of Sorcery (Charlotte, NC: Entertainment Concepts, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1630)
    - Space Warrior (Raleigh, NC: Argon Games), 1980 (Volume M2)
    - Spacefarers Guide to Alien Monsters (Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games), 1979 (Volume 1654)
    - Spacefarers Guide to Alien Races (Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games), 1979 (Volume 1655)
    - Spacefarers Guide to Planets: Sector One (Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games), 1978 (Volume 1656)
    - Spacefarers Guide to Sector Two (Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games), 1979 (Volume 1657)
    - Starfaring (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1976 (Volume 1672)
    - Starships and Spacemen (Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1978 (Volume 1673)
    - Supergame (Santa Monica, CA: Dag Design), 1980 (Volume 1071)
    - Superhero 2044 (no city: Gamescience, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1678)
    - Swordplay (unknown), undated (Volume M2)
    - Tegal Manor (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1549)
    - Temple, Book 1 (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1776)
    - The Adventure of the Jade Jaguar (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1075)
    - The Astrogators Chartbook (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1772)
    - The Black Tower (San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press), 1981 (Volume 1600)
    - The Book of Shamans (Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games), 1978 (Volume 1570)
    - The Book of Treasure (Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games), 1978 (Volume 1572)
    - The Book of Treasure Maps III (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1464)
    - The City of Carse (San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press), 1980 (Volume 1602)
    - The City of Carse, 2nd ed. (San Diego, CA: Midkemia Press), 1980 (Volume 1457)
    - The Compendium of Weapons, Armour and Castles (Detroit, MI: Palladium Books), 1989 (Volume 1614)
    - The Compleat Fantasist: How to Convert the Major Fantasy Role Playing Systems to Each Other (Englewood, CO: Dimension Six, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1571)
    - The Complete Warlock (Long Beach, CA: Balboa Game Co. ), 1978 (Volume 1623)
    - The Curse on Hareth (Bath, ME: The Companions Inc.), 1982 (Volume M3)
    - The D6 System: The Customizable Roleplaying Game (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 242)
    - The Demon Pits of Caeldo (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd. ), 1983 (Volume 1172)
    - The Dungeon Masters Survival Kit (Portland, OR: Sage Lore Productions Inc.), undated (Volume M4)
    - The Emerald Tablet (New York, NY: Creative Wargames Workshop, Inc.), 1977 (Volume 1697)
    - The Fantasy Cartographer's Field Book (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1773)
    - The Fighter (Killeen, TX: Martian Game Modules), 1979 (Volume M4)
    - The First Fantasy Campaign (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1977 (Volume 1637)
    - The Giant Robot Role Playing and Battle Game: Robot Warriors (#27) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1986 (Volume 2129)
    - The Gods vs. Chaos in Deadly Final Conflict: Viking Gods Minigame (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1982 (Volume M2)
    - The Handbook of Traps and Tricks (Abilene, TX: Dragon Tree Press), 1981 (Volume 1725)
    - The Legacy of Zorro (no city: Fusion Labs Group), 2001 (Volume 1599)
    - The Lost Abbey of Calthonwey (Rockville, MD: Phoenix Games), 1979 (Volume 1173)